- Well, we've also got
another fine guitar player
with us on this tour, and
that's Danny "Kooch" Kortchmar.
Danny, come on out.
(audience applauding)
You want some notes, too?
Okay. Pick a note.
That's a good note.
(piano note reverberates)
(gentle music)
Close enough for jazz.
We're gonna do a song for
you called "It's Too Late."
(gentle music)
♪ Stayed in bed all mornin'
just to pass the time ♪
♪ There's somethin' wrong
here there can be no denyin' ♪
♪ One of us is changin' ♪
♪ Or maybe we've just stopped tryin' ♪
♪ And it's too late,
baby, now it's too late ♪
♪ Though we really did try to make it ♪
♪ Somethin' inside has died ♪
♪ And I can't hide and
I just can't fake it ♪
♪ Oh, no, no, no, no, no ♪
(Carole vocalizing)
♪ It used to be so easy
livin' here with you ♪
♪ You were light and breezy
and I knew just what to do ♪
♪ Now you look so unhappy
and I feel like a fool ♪
♪ And it's too late,
baby, now it's too late ♪
♪ Though we really did try to make it ♪
♪ Somethin' inside has died ♪
♪ And I can't hide and
I just can't fake it ♪
♪ Oh, no ♪
♪ No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no ♪
♪ No, no, no ♪
♪ Doo doo doo doo doo la la doo da da ♪
♪ Da da da da da da la ♪
(gentle guitar and piano music)
(Carole vocalizing)
♪ There'll be good times
again for me and you ♪
♪ But we just can't stay together ♪
♪ Don't ya feel it, too ♪
♪ Still I'm glad for what we
had and how I once loved you ♪
♪ But it's too late,
baby, now it's too late ♪
♪ Though we really did try to make it ♪
♪ Somethin' inside has died ♪
♪ And I can't hide and
I just can't fake it ♪
♪ Oh, no, no, no, no, no ♪
♪ No, no, no, no, no, no, no ♪
♪ Doo doo doo doo doo
doo la la doo da da ♪
♪ Da da da na na na na la ♪
♪ It's too late, baby ♪
♪ It's too late, oh now, darlin' ♪
♪ It's too late ♪
(audience applauding)
Thank you.